Guide to the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection RG.11.4
New York University Archives
- Series XI: Building files: Washington Square Center
  - 528-530 West Broadway -- Classroom, Office Conversion, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Building files: University Heights Center
  - Aerospace Laboratory, Jan 1964-Sep 1964 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Aerospace Laboratory, Oct 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Aerospace Laboratory - Harlem River Site, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Altschul House, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Begrisch Hall, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Letter from Jennifer Hughes to Leon Brand, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bishop's House [1970 Loring Place], 1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Butler Hall, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Campus Projects/Landscaping, 1961-1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Campus Projects/Landscaping -- with Russell Page Corresp., 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Clocks, Plaques, and Sculpture -- including American Artist Hall of Fame Busts, 1966-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dormitory and Parking Garage Complex, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1964
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Memo from Hamilton P. Smith to Mr. Beck for Distribution, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Memo from Hamilton P. Smith to (Please list Addressees), 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Transmittal of Photocopied Letter from Polly Theban to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Transmittal of Memo from Polly Theban to Martin Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Joseph E.Schober to Marcel Breuer, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to T. Papachristou, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Martin L. Beck, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Technical Salaries through June 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Letter from John M. O'Mara to Marcel Breuer, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Dormitory and Parking Garage Complex, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Memo from Julian Neski to Mr. Roberto, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to John M. O'Mara, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Annotated Letter from Tician Papachristou to John M. O'Mara, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Julian J. Neski to Joseph Roberto, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to John M. O'Mara, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Julian J. Neski to Martin Beck, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Tician Papachristou, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Invoice #1230, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Martin L. Beck, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to "Gentlemen", 1965 (Box 25)
    - Invoice For Professional Services, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Invoice For Professional Services, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Letter from "ar" to Marcel Breuer, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Letter from "ar" to Marcel Breuer (dupe), 1966 (Box 25)
  - Engineering Building (Proposed), 1947-1950 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Engineering Center (Proposed), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Housing, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Gould Dormitory, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Gould Dormitory, Jan 1962-Apr 1962 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Gould Dormitory, May 1962-Jul 1962 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Gould Dormitory, Aug 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Gould Dormitory -- Specifications, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Gould Dormitory, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Gould Dormitory, Apr 1963-Dec 1964 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Gould Dormitory, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Gould Hall of Technology/Tech I -- Spectrograph Facility, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Gould Hall of Technology/Tech I, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Letter from Marcel Breuer to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Gould Library, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Gould Library -- renovations planning, 1969 firebombing, 1965-1969 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Apr 1963-Jun 1963 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Jul 1963-Aug 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Sep 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Jan 1964-Mar 1964 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, Apr 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Gould Student Center -- Addition, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Gould Student Center -- Terrace Landscaping, Driveway, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Group Living Plan II -- Pi Lambda Phi Fraternity, 1961-1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Group Living Plan II -- Pi Lambda Phi Fraternity -- Specifications, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Guard Booth, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Guggenheim Building, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics -- Expansion Planning, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Hall of Fame, 1961-1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Hall of Fame -- Landscaping, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Havemeyer Annex, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Havemeyer Annex, Jan 1963-May 1963 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Havemeyer Annex, Jun 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Havemeyer Annex, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Havemeyer Building, 1961-1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - History House [194 West 180th Street], 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Language Hall, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Library (Proposed), 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Life Sciences Building, 1963-1966 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Loring Place Gate, Stairs, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Loew Hall -- Vice Chancellor Voorhis File, 1953-1955 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Loew Hall, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - MacCracken Hall, 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Mechanical Engineering Building, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Multiple Buildings/Miscellaneous, 1961-1977 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Nichols Chemistry Building, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Nuclear Reactor Facilities, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Field -- Lighting, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Old Engineering Building, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Parking Lot, Andrews Avenue, 1964-1969 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Parking, General, 1960-1968 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Patterson Reserve (ROTC) Center, 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Philosophy Hall, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Philosophy Hall, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Radio Station (WNYU) Studio, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Research Engineering Buildings, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sage Building -- Science Library, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 2217 Sedgewick Avenue -- Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sedgewick Avenue Dormitory [North Hall], 1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sedgewick Avenue Dormitory [North Hall], 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sedgewick Avenue Dormitory [North Hall] -- Meeting Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Service Building, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Signs and Plaques, 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - University Heights- Silver Residence Hall and Flagpoles, 1961 - 1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Transmittal of Paving Details from Richard Cortez to Joseph Roberto, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Letter from Joseph J. Roberto to Hamilton Smith, 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph E. Schober to Marcel Breuer, 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to "Gentlemen", 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Murray S. Emslie to Martin L. Beck, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Murry S. Emslie, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Letter from Robert F. Gatje to Chester D. Onderdonk, 1959 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Murray S. Emslie to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Invoice for Technical Salaries to Marcel Breuer, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer (Box 27)
    - Letter from Marin L. Beck to Murray S. Emslie, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Murray S. Emslie to Joseph E. Schober, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Panel Drawings from Murray S. Emslie to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Murray S. Emslie, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Letter from Murray S. Emslie to Howard Dressner, Office of University Development, NYU, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from James M. hester to Marcel Breuer, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Residence Hall Drawings from H.S. to Martin Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin l. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - South Hall, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - State Hall -- condition, proposed demolition for parking lot, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Stevenson House -- Faculty Club, Provost's Office, 1962-1966 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1961 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1962 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Technology II Pilot Scheme Invoice, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph J. Roberto to Hamilton Smith, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton Smith to Chencellor Stoddard et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. beck, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton Smith to Chancellor Stoddard et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton Smith to Dean Ragazzini et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Marcel Breuer to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton Smith to Dr. Stoddard et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Memo from Hamilton Smith to Chanecellor Stoddard et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Professor Sidney G. Roth, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Memo from Hamilton Smith to Dean Knedler et al, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Martin L. Beck to Joseph J. Roberto, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from J.W. Knedler Jr. to Hamilton Smith, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Memo from Hamilton Smith to Chancellor George D. Stoddard et al, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Photostat of Memo from Hamilton Smith to Chancellor Stoddard et al (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Invoice # 1031 to Marcel Breuer for Professional Services Rendered, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1030 to Marcel Breuer for Services Rendered (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Tech II Pilot Scheme Presentation from Hamilton Smith to Martin l. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Floor Plans from Hamilton Smith to Martin Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Norman S. Briskman, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of letter from Norman S. Briskman to Hamilton Smith, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Space allocation diagram from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Memo to Mr. Hamilton Smith from Dean J.W. Knedler, Jr., 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, November 19, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - NYU - Tech. II Building Cost Estimate Data, November 19, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer and Associates, June 4, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Letter from Marcel Breuer to Martin L. Beck, September 18, 1962 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean Robert Geldmacher, November 9, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Tech II - NSF Submission - Outline Specification Data, Undated (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 22 October 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton P. Smith, 19 October 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 15 October 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 12 October 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 16 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean Robert Geldmacher, 15 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 14 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 27 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin l. Beck to Hamilton P. Smith, 24 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean John Ragazzini et al, 18 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean John Ragazzini et al, August 20, 1964
    - Tech II NSF Submission - Cost Estimate Data, 20 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 20 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Tech. II - NSF Submission - Cost Estimate Data (Annotated), August 20, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 19 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Tech. II - NSF Submission - Outline Specification Data, 19 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Photostat of Letter from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean Robert Goldmacher, 22 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean John Ragazzini, 19 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Tech.II - NSF Submission - Outline Specification Data, Undated (Box 27)
    - Letter from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean Robert Goldmacher, 22 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - Transmittal of Site and Floor Plans from Stanley E. Abercrombie to Martin Beck, 17 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean John Ragazzini et al, 5 August 1964 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Stanley Abercrombie to Dean John Ragazzini et al, 26 June 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 16 June 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck (Annotated), 16 June 1964 (Box 27)
    - For Reimbursable Expenses to Marcel Breuer, 10 September 1964 (Box 27)
    - For Technical Salaries - to Marcel Breuer, 22 October 1964 (Box 27)
    - For Reimbursable Expenses to Marcel Breuer, 2 December 1964 (Box 27)
    - For Technical Salaries to Marcel Breuer, 15 December 1964 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton Smith to Martin Beck, 28 December 1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Memo from Martin L. Beck to Dr. Peter Agnew, 19 January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin Beck, 1 February 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton P. Smith, 5 February 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 9 February 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 10 February 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 11 February 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Martin L. Beck, 2 March 1965 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1161 For Technical Salaries to Marcel Breuer, 1 March 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Peter L. Agnew to Marcel Breuer, 4 March 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papchristou to Martin L. Beck, 11 March 1965 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1169 for PRIMARY PAYMENT to Marcel Breuer, 12 March 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph E. Schober to Tician Papachristou, 2 April 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Joseph R. Loring & Associates, 7 April 1965 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton P.Smith to Dean Ragazzini et al, 8 April 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean Geldmacher, 9 April 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 13 April 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Botho C. Schneider to Martin Beck, 4 May 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 21 May 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated), 21 May 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Boto C. Schneider to Norman S. Briskman, 2 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton P. Smith to Dean Ragazzini, 7 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 4 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Marvin Belcher, 8 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter to Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 8 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph E.Schober to Hamilton P. Smith, 9 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 14 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 14 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 16 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated), 16 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Dr. Joseph Schober, 17 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papchristou to Martin L. Beck, 18 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1191 For Professional Services Rendered to Marcel Breuer, 18 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 25 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Tician Papachristou, 22 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 23 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Botho Schneider to Martin L. Beck
    - Invoice #1191 For Professional Services Rendered to Marcel Breuer, 23 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 30 June 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph E. Schober to Hamilton Smith, 30 June 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], Jul 1965-Aug 1965 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 12 July 1965 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 13 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Mr. Joseph Roberto (Annotated), 14 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Mr. Joseph Roberto, 14 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph J. Roberto to Hamilton P. Smith, 15 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papachristou to Dr. Joseph E. Schober, 23 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Minutes of Meeting Held 20 July 1965 (Tech. II Project), 23 July 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Merwin Belcher to Mr. B. Schneider, 3 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Tician Papchristou to Martin L. Beck, 12 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1208 for Reimbursable Expenses to Marcel Breuer, 12 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 13 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 17 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 23 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated), 23 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Marcel Breuer to Dr. Russell D. Niles, 26 August 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Werner A. Baum to Marcel Breuer, 30 August 1965 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], Sep 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Letter from Marcel Breuer to Werner A. Baum, 3 September 1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Invoice #1217 for Dormitory and Parking Area, 9 September 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 20 Septmeber 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Tician Papachristou, 13 October 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 3 November 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Mr. C. Edward Enroth, 9 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Mr. C. Edward Enroth (Annotated), 9 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Russell D. Niles to Hamilton P. Smith, 16 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith (Annotated Draft), Undated (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Chancellor Russell D. Niles, 22 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated 1), 23 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated 2), 23 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (Annotated 3), 23 December 1965 (Box 27)
    - Tech. II Building - Preliminary Outline Specifications (Annotated), 14 June 1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II] -- Grant Application, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II] -- Construction Grant Application, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II] -- Loan, Grant Applications, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Technology Building II [Tech II], 1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 3 January 1966 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 7 January 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Russell D. Niles to Hamilton P. Smith, 11 January 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 7 January 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from John M. O'Mara to Hamilton Smith, 1 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from John M. O'Mara to Hamilton Smith, 14 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck, 11 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Martin L. Beck (with Approval), 11 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to John M. O'Mara COPY, 18 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to John M. O'Mara, 18 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Joseph J. Roberto to Marcel Breuer, 28 February 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to Joseph J. Roberto, 9 March 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer and Associates to VP Werner Baum, 31 March 1966 (Box 27)
    - Invoice #1279 for Professional Services Rendered, 1 April 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Werner A. Baum to Hamilton P. Smith, 4 April 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from John M. O'Mara to Hamilton P. Smith, 11 April 1966 (Box 27)
    - Memo from Marcel Breuer to Dean John Ragazzini and Dean Robert Geldmacher, 29 April 1966 (Box 27)
    - Letter from Hamilton P. Smith to John O'Mara, 5 May 1966 (Box 27)